[Unsoiled Starlight]
[Episode 25]
[Adapted from Migu's novel
"Unsoiled Starlight"]
[Original Writer: Shan Gu Jun]
How rare.
I thought all your time now
belonged to Shu Tinglan.
These photos.
It was you that gave them
to my mother, right?
I was that boring?
[Senzhou Bank Transaction Record]
After all, in this world,
the person who hates my wife,
other than you, her half-sister,
there won't be a second one.
Wen Jian.
Enough is enough.
Enough?
Why should I?
I just want everything she has
to become precarious.
I want every time she gains something
to be accompanied
by the fear of losing it.
Why?
Just because of your father?
Father?
Does he even deserve the title?
I have never fought for a father's love.
I just want an answer.
I want to know.
Why is it that we
share the same blood,
yet Shu Tinglan is a treasure
out in the open,
but me?
From the moment I was born I'm a mistake
that should have been erased.
Wen Jian.
This is not an excuse for you
to hurt others.
And Tinglan shouldn't have to bear it.
You also think I'm looking for excuses,
don't you, Zhuo Yu'an?
No.
I'm just walking a path
that was destined long ago.
Shu Tinglan, on this path,
is the brightest lamp,
and I'm just a shadow under the lamp
that no one notices.
I just want to try.
If I smash the lamp,
will everyone be able to
see me at a glance?
This has nothing to do with me.
And even less to do with her.
See?
You are just like them, Zhuo Yu'an.
Just as cruel.
No difference.
Recently, a tech company
hired me as a consultant.
The next time we meet,
we will be competitors.
Dong.
This color looks good, right?
Yes.
Who are you knitting this for?
For Tinglan's future baby.
Dong.
Do you think I will recover
from this illness?
Of course!
Once you finish knitting the sweater,
you can give it to
your daughter's baby
when you are discharged.
I'm not leaving the hospital.
I don't want to bother Tinglan.
How are the preparations
for the trial going?
I've found some breakthroughs,
but I need to verify them one by one.
Not bad.
If you have any questions,
feel free to talk to me anytime.
Okay.
This is not just your fault.
Don't put too much pressure on yourself.
After all,
this is the first case
I've handled independently.
No matter what,
I will take responsibility to the end.
Remember to eat.
It's all messed up.
It's unwearable.
It's not knitted right.
It's almost done.
Mom.
It's ruined.
Mom!
It's ruined!
It's okay, it's okay!
-It's unwearable！
-We will buy a new one.
-Mom!
-I need to knit it!
Mom, look at me.
I'm Tinglan.
Forget it! Let's buy a new one!
-Forget it!
-No! I'll fix it!
Mom!
-It’s almost done!
-Mom!
I'm Tinglan.
Mommy...
Mommy.
Mom...
I'm Tinglan.
Tinglan.
We're not staying here anymore.
Let's go home, okay?
I don't want to go back.
Tinglan, Mom is doing fine here.
I don't want to go home.
Going home will only burden you.
You're not a burden to me.
Let's go. Let's go home.
I don't want to go home.
Tinglan.
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
I talked to Wen Jian yesterday.
Maybe I was too harsh
and provoked her,
so she came to bother your mother.
This is between me and Wen Jian.
It's not your fault.
By the way,
Mom said
it's been a long time
since she hung out with me,
so she wants to go out to relax.
Okay.
I'll walk together.
No need.
You're so busy with work.
We'll only be gone for a day or two.
I have a court hearing next Monday.
All right.
Be careful on the road.
Call me when you get there.
Zhuo Yu'an.
Thank you.
Hello?
Is this Miss Shu?
Yes.
May I ask who is calling?
My name is Zhuo Hong.
I'm Yu'an's father.
It's okay.
I'm here.
I think
Tinglan is a nice girl.
She's capable and innocent.
Why do you insist
on opposing her being with our son?
I heard from Wang
that you even sent someone
to investigate her friend's company.
You're way too involved, aren't you?
You don't understand.
Miss Shu,
didn't I tell you
to come alone?
When you called her,
I was right there.
I thought it would be more appropriate
for us to come together.
You are Shu Minghai's daughter.
Back then, your father almost dragged
half of Zhuo Group into the mud.
If I hadn't used
my old connections and last resorts,
the place you're standing right now
would have changed hands long ago.
Uncle Zhuo.
As for what my father did,
I can't
and won't defend him.
But I am me.
His blood flows in your veins,
and you have a mentally unstable mother.
Miss Shu.
I didn't call you here today
to discuss
right and wrong with you.
I just want to tell you
that some things can be inherited.
For example,
the instinct for treachery.
Uncle Zhuo.
I can't choose my background,
but you shouldn't
deny everything about me because of it.
Even if you don't believe me,
you should trust
Zhuo Yu'an's judgment.
Our relationship is a choice we both made.
You shouldn't
use "doing good for Zhuo Yu'an"
as an excuse
to control his life.
I know
you're afraid of anything uncontrollable.
But this is unfair to us.
You're also a coward.
Sharp-tongued.
Just like your father!
Sign the divorce agreement today,
and I'll let go of the past.
Do you really think
you can control everything about me?
Including my life
and my choices?
I spent twenty years
raising you to be someone everyone envies.
Now I won't allow anyone to hurt you.
Do you understand?
Do you really think
you can do whatever you want?
Have you forgotten
how the Zhuo Group came to be?
Back then, you were just a poor boy
with nothing to your name.
When you were living off my mom,
did you ever consider her feelings?
You...
How can you talk to your dad like that?
Zhuo.
It's OK.
Calm down.
Zhuo.
Zhuo!
What's wrong, Zhuo?
Dad!
Zhuo!
Your dad...
He's not breathing!
Doctor!
Zhuo!
Zhuo, don't scare me!
Move!
Let me take a look.
Zhuo...
-Don’t scare me.
-Hello, is this 120?
-Someone is having a heart attack here.
-Zhuo...
-Please come here right now.
-Wake up! Wake up!
[Blessing Peace]
[0707]
Be careful.
Are you feeling a bit better?
It's okay.